Reading Art: Art for Book Lovers is a celebration of an everyday object — the book, represented here in almost three hundred artworks from museums around the world.
《阅读艺术：献给爱书人的艺术》是对一种日常物品——书——的礼赞；这本画册收录了来自世界各地博物馆的近300件艺术作品，书的形象就呈现在这些作品之中。
The image of the reader appears throughout history, in art made long before books as we now know them came into being.
读者的形象贯穿古今：早在我们今天所熟知的这种书籍问世很久以前，艺术作品中就已出现了读者的身影。
In artists’ representations of books and reading, we see moments of shared humanity that go beyond culture and time.
在艺术家对书籍和阅读的描绘中，我们看到了体现人类共同天性、超越文化与时代的瞬间。
In this “book of books,” artworks are selected and arranged in a way that emphasizes these connections between different eras and cultures.
在这本“书中之书”里，艺术作品的挑选和编排方式突出了不同时代、不同文化之间的这些联系。
We see scenes of children learning to read at home or at school, with the book as a focus for relations between the generations.
我们看到孩子们在家中或学校里学习阅读的场景，书在其中成为代际关系的焦点。
Adults are portrayed alone in many settings and poses — absorbed in a volume, deep in thought or lost in a moment of leisure.
艺术家笔下的成年人则独自一人，身处各种环境，姿态各异——或沉浸在书中，或陷入沉思，或沉醉于片刻的闲暇。
These scenes may have been painted hundreds of years ago, but they record moments we can all relate to.
这些场景可能是几百年前画的，但它们记录下的是我们都能感同身受的时刻。
Books themselves may be used symbolically in paintings to demonstrate the intellect, wealth or faith of the subject.
在绘画中，书本身也可能被用作象征，来展示画中人物的才智、财富或信仰。
Before the wide use of the printing press, books were treasured objects and could be works of art in their own right.
在印刷机广泛使用之前，书是人们珍视的物品，其本身就可能是艺术品。
More recently, as books have become inexpensive or even throwaway, artists have used them as the raw material for artworks — transforming covers, pages or even complete volumes into paintings and sculptures.
近来，随着书变得便宜，甚至成了用完就扔的东西，艺术家们便把书用作艺术创作的原材料——把封面、书页甚至整本书改造成绘画和雕塑。
Continued developments in communication technologies were once believed to make the printed page outdated.
人们曾经认为，通信技术的不断发展会让印刷读物过时。
From a 21st-century point of view, the printed book is certainly ancient, but it remains as interactive as any battery-powered e-reader.
从21世纪的视角来看，印刷书籍无疑是古老的，但它依然和任何一台电池驱动的电子阅读器一样具有互动性。
To serve its function, a book must be activated by a user: the cover opened, the pages parted, the contents reviewed, perhaps notes written down or words underlined.
书要发挥作用，就必须由使用者来激活：掀开封面，翻开书页，浏览内容，或许还要记下笔记或在字词下画线。
And in contrast to our increasingly networked lives where the information we consume is monitored and tracked, a printed book still offers the chance of a wholly private, “off-line” activity.
我们的生活日益网络化，所获取的信息受到监控和追踪；与之相比，印刷书籍仍让人有机会进行完全私密的“离线”活动。